(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
声出し応援 OK です
Please be aware of flashing lights.
Cheering loudly is okay.
Cheering loudly is ok.
hololive 5th fes. Capture the Moment
オフィシャルグッズ販売期間
Official Merchandise Sales Period
The concert will be starting soon.
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
Due to production reasons, please be aware of flashing lights.
声出し応援 OK です
Vocal cheering is OK.
バンダイ、バンダイスピリッツより
From Bandai and Bandai Spirits,
エキスポ会場でも展示中の
we're introducing products currently
商品をご紹介。
on display at the Expo venue.
ガシャポンや一番くじなど、たくさんの商品が発売いたします。
Gashapon, Ichiban Kuji, and many other products will be released.
バンダイブース、BANDAI SPIRITSブースでは、会場限定グッズも無料配布中！
At the Bandai booth and BANDAI SPIRITS booth, venue-exclusive goods are also being distributed for free!
プレバンではすぐに使えるクーポンももらえるチャンス！
At P-Bandai, you also have a chance to get coupons that can be used immediately!
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Weiß Schwarz!
楽しむ準備はいい？
Are you ready to enjoy?
ヴァイスシュヴァルツの舞台でも、青春しよう！
Let's have a youth on the stage of Weiß Schwarz too!
プレミアムブースター、ホロライブプロダクション サマーコレクション、3月22日（金）発売！
Premium Booster, hololive production Summer Collection, on sale March 22nd (Fri)!
ブシロード！
Bushiroad!
ホロスターズが、ヴァイスシュヴァルツブラウに登場！
HOLOSTARS appear in Weiß Schwarz Blau!
ようこそ、カードゲームの舞台へ！
Welcome to the stage of card games!
ヴァイスシュヴァルツブラウ スタートデッキ&ブースターパック ホロスターズ、好評発売中！
Weiß Schwarz Blau Start Deck & Booster Pack HOLOSTARS, now on sale!
ブシロード！
Bushiroad!
hololive SUPER EXPO 2024 開催を記念して、ホロライブメンバーのねんどろいどが、新衣装になって再登場！
To commemorate hololive SUPER EXPO 2024, Nendoroids of hololive members are returning in new outfits!
新しいねんどろいどもお楽しみに！
Look forward to the new Nendoroids too!
フリューから「ホロライブ」プライズが、全国アミューズメント施設に続々登場！
hololive prizes from FuRyu are appearing one after another in amusement facilities nationwide!
今後国内のホロライブメンバー全員展開予定！
All domestic hololive members are planned to be released in the future!
フリュー！
FuRyu!
彼女たちと一緒に夢をつめこんだ、胸がときめく新たなブランド。
A heart-pounding new brand filled with dreams together with them.
hololive 5th fes. Capture the Moment
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
Attention For Visitors
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援 OK です
Cheering loudly is OK.
マスクの着用はお客様の任意でお願いいたします
You are free to wear a mask during the show.
hololive 5th fes. Capture the Moment オフィシャルグッズ
hololive 5th fes. Capture the Moment Official Goods
オフィシャルグッズ販売期間
Official Goods Sales Period
バンダイ、バンダイスピリッツより
From Bandai and Bandai Spirits...
EXPO 会場でも展示中の商品をご紹介！
...we introduce products on display at the EXPO venue!
ウエハースやデフォルメコレクション、
Wafers, Deformed Collections,
ARTグミ、カードダス、
ART Gummy, Carddass,
各 EC サイトで予約受付中！
Now accepting pre-orders on various EC sites!
くじなど、たくさんの商品が発売いたします。
Lottery and many other products will be released.
会場限定でプレゼント！
Prizes limited to the venue!
バンダイ / BANDAI SPIRITS ブースでは会場限定グッズも無料配布中！
At the Bandai / BANDAI SPIRITS booths, venue-limited goods are being distributed for free!
プレバンではすぐに使えるクーポンももらえる！
You can also get coupons that can be used immediately at P-Bandai!
バンダイ！
Bandai!
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ
Weiss Schwarz
楽しむ準備はいい？
Are you ready to have fun?
ヴァイスシュヴァルツの舞台でも、青春しよう。
Let's have some youth on the Weiss Schwarz stage too.
いっしょに遊ぼう！
Let's play together!
プレミアムブースター
Premium Booster
ホロライブプロダクション サマーコレクション 3月22日金発売
hololive production Summer Collection. On sale March 22nd (Fri).
ブシロード！
Bushiroad!
ホロスターズがヴァイスシュヴァルツブラウに登場！
HOLOSTARS makes its debut in Weiss Schwarz Blau!
ようこそ、カードゲームの舞台へ。
Welcome to the card game stage.
ヴァイスシュヴァルツブラウ
Weiss Schwarz Blau
スタートデッキ＆ブースターパック、ホロスターズ、好評発売中！
Start Deck & Booster Pack: HOLOSTARS, now on sale!
ブシロード！
Bushiroad!
ホロライブスーパーエキスポ2024開催を記念して
To commemorate hololive SUPER EXPO 2024,
ホロライブメンバーのねんどろいどが新衣装になって再登場！
hololive members' Nendoroids are back in their new outfits!
新しいねんどろいどもお楽しみに。
Please look forward to the new Nendoroids.
グッドスマイルカンパニー。
Good Smile Company.
フリューから「ホロライブ」プライズが全国アミューズメント施設に。
FuRyu 'hololive' prizes coming to amusement facilities nationwide.
2024年7月以降に続々登場！
Releasing one after another from July 2024 onwards!
今後国内のホロライブメンバー全員展開予定！
All domestic hololive members are scheduled to be featured in the future!
フリュー！
FuRyu!
a
推しの曲、めっちゃいいね！
This favorite song is really good!
みるハコチャーン！
Miruhako-chaaan!
みるハコなら臨場感たっぷりで推しのコンテンツが楽しめる。
With Miruhako, you can enjoy your favorite content with a full sense of presence.
みるハコ最高！
Miruhako is the best!
音も増やそう！
Let's turn up the sound!
みるハコ by JOYSOUND
Miruhako by JOYSOUND
予約受付中！ 予約締切 5月31日(金) ホロライブ 星街すいせい 1/7スケールフィギュア
Pre-orders now open! Deadline: May 31st (Fri). hololive Hoshimachi Suisei 1/7 Scale Figure
New Project hololive 24 CITY 2024 Summer
彼女たちと一緒に 夢をつめこんだ 胸がときめく新たなブランド IoloReuve
Together with them, a new brand filled with dreams that makes the heart flutter. IoloReuve
ReGLOSS 2nd Single「シンメトリー」 Digital Release 2024.03.24(SUN) 0:00
ReGLOSS 2nd Single 'Symmetry'. Digital Release: 2024.03.24 (SUN) 0:00
Capture The Moment
Capture the Moment / hololive 5th fes.
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
Attention For Visitors
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援 OK です ※マスクの着用はお客様の任意でお願いいたします
Cheering loudly is OK. *You are free to wear a mask during the show.
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is OK. *You are free to wear a mask during the show.
hololive 5th fes. Capture the Moment Official Goods
hololive 5th fes. Capture the Moment
I'm excited to see AZKi perform on hololive HoneyWorks stage! By FranFreesia
Mumei, Stage 2 Ganbare!! You are the best idol! I'm always rooting for you. Fran Trahant
Mumei, Stage 2 Good Luck!! You are the best idol! I'm always rooting for you. Fran Trahant
Hi!
Mumei! Finally! I can see you! I'll cheer you on with all my heart!
Say!
Don't worry, it's gonna be the greatest show! Selamat bersenang-senang! by k-7
Don't worry, it's gonna be the greatest show! Have fun! by k-7
Hi! Hi!
Capture the Moment! 素晴らしい1日を思い出に残そう！
Capture the Moment! Let's make this wonderful day a memorable one!
1, 2!
I will continue to support you! Saya akan terus mendukung Anda! by CharaHarma
I will continue to support you! I will always support you! by CharaHarma
Go!
I'm so excited to watch IRyS perform! Ganbare IRyS! Numa Loo
I'm so excited to watch IRyS perform! Go for it, IRyS! Numa Loo
Yes!
I'm so happy to finally see all my oshis on stage, you're gonna rock it, IRyS! -- SimbaPalsy
I'm so happy to finally see all my favorites on stage, you're gonna rock it, IRyS! -- SimbaPalsy
Let's go!
Ready?
Wish everyone the best and have fun on shore! Cheers! -- Allsar11
Hi!
Can't wait to see your idol on stage since last year! Let's Capture the MOMENT! by Heaman fanclub
Jump!
Say!
Yes, I'm really looking forward to seeing you during holofes! I hope you have a lot of fun! Edu Lima
Go!
Keep shining bright, Hololive! Your fans are behind you all the way! -- Solaria
Hey!
Hi! Hi!
I can't wait to see your performance on stage! You are a new star! Do your best, IRyS!! -- ErikButho
1, 2!
Hope it's a fantastic performance! Enjoy your show, Kobo! -- Sword Ark
Yes!
Go!
Gura! Your journey is an inspiration to us. Stay strong and keep playing! -- IRAN
Hi!
Hope it's a fantastic performance! Enjoy your show, Kanata! -- Sword Ark
Ready?
Say!
I'm not sure if the stage can handle the heat! You'll bring down the house! -- GoldenEmi
Go!
Zeta! Congrats on your 1st 3D concert! I know you're gonna nail it! Ganbare! -- GoldenEmi
Zeta! Congrats on your 1st 3D concert! I know you're gonna nail it! Good luck! -- GoldenEmi
Hey!
Let's go!
Found Sweeny! I'll be cheering you on for all the saplings in Singapore! You got this, Fauna! -- Evan C
Hi! Hi!
Everyone let's goooooo!!! I will cheer for you all! -- Jimmy H
Yes!
1, 2!
Have some fun and rock the stage again this year! -- Bivanalic
Go!
IRyS!!! Your music is as impactful as it is beautiful. Bringing us joys and matters, a smile. IRyS Ch.
Say!
完璧で究極のビジネスパートナー miComet
Perfect and ultimate business partners: miComet
stage3 はじまんぼう
Stage 3 is about to start!
フブキ好きだ!!
I love Fubuki!!
ホロリスも好きだ!!
I love Hololis too!!
Uuuu
Cheer for your Oshi and Have fun! Ameeee Love <3
白上フブキ
Shirakami Fubuki
湊あくあ
Minato Aqua
紫咲シオン
Murasaki Shion
百鬼あやめ
Nakiri Ayame
AZKi
さくらみこ
Sakura Miko
猫又おかゆ
Nekomata Okayu
星街すいせい
Hoshimachi Suisei
常闇トワ
Tokoyami Towa
雪花ラミィ
Yukihana Lamy
ラプラス・ダークネス
La+ Darknesss
ムーナ・ホシノヴァ
Moona Hoshinova
クレイジー・オリー
Kureiji Ollie
アーニャ・メルフィッサ
Anya Melfissa
ワトソン・アメリア
Watson Amelia
セレス・ファウナ
Ceres Fauna
七詩ムメイ
Nanashi Mumei
生まれ立てのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our fresh excitement resound
最高の時間、最高の仲間と
A superb time with superb friends
煌めきに乗って
Riding on the sparkle
Yeah!
憶えてるかな？ 最初の歌
Do you remember? That first song
懐かしいね
It brings back memories
私の声が 震えていた
My voice was trembling
懐かしい
Nostalgic
あの日から続く今が 今
The "now" that started from that day, is now
みんなと掴んだ今日だよ
Today is the day we seized together
もっともっともっともっと
More, more, more, more
加速するハート
Accelerating hearts
一緒に行くよ どこまでも
We'll go together, anywhere
準備はOK？
Are you ready?
開け 夢の扉を
Open the door to dreams
いつだって煌めきたいんだ
I always want to sparkle
生まれ立てのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our fresh excitement resound
最高の時間、最高の仲間と
A superb time with superb friends
ここにいるよ 見つけてくれたから
I'm here because you found me
君に会いたくてやってきたんだ
I came here because I wanted to see you
みんなで歌おう
Let's all sing together
終わらないメロディ
An unending melody
煌めきに乗って
Riding on the sparkle
Yeah!
届いてるかな？ 私の声
Is it reaching you? My voice
きっと
Surely
届けたいのは 君に笑顔
What I want to deliver is a smile to you
No smile
理想通りにいかなくて 悔しくて
When things didn't go as planned, it was frustrating
みんなと泣き笑ったんだ
But we laughed and cried together
ぎゅっとぎゅっとぎゅっと
Tight, tight, tight
全て抱きしめて
Holding it all close
行こうどこまでも
Let's go, wherever
準備はOK？
Are you ready?
進め希望の道を
Move forward on the path of hope
1, 2, 3 きらめきライター
1, 2, 3 Sparkling Lighter
好きな気持ちカラフルに奏でたいな
I want to play my feelings of love colorfully
最高の場所最高の仲間と
At the best place, with the best friends
ここにいるよ幻なんかじゃない
We're here, it's not a phantom
君の心が幸せに染まるように
So that your heart may be colored with happiness
重ねてくハーモニー
Layering harmonies
きらめきまとって
Wearing the sparkle
歌い続けたいな
I want to keep singing
踊り続けたいな
I want to keep dancing
そんな願いわがままもいいでしょう
Such a wish, being selfish is okay, right?
だって楽しすぎて止まらない
Because it's so fun, I can't stop
輝くステージもっともっと
The shining stage, more and more
お願いずっと
Please, forever
イェーイ！
Yay!
嬉しい楽しいだけじゃ語れない
It's more than just being happy and fun
今も今も悩みはあるけど
Even now, even now, there are worries, but...
ここにいるよ
I'm here
私ここにいるよ
I'm right here
君と同じ世界を見つめて
Looking at the same world as you
行くよ！きらめきライター
Here we go! Sparkling Lighter
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let the fresh excitement resonate
最高な時間最高の仲間と
The best time with the best friends
ここにいるよ見つけてくれたから
I'm here because you found me
君に会いたくてやってきたんだみんなで歌おう
I came here because I wanted to see you, let's all sing
せーの！
One, two!
終わらないメロディきらめきに乗って
An endless melody, riding on the sparkle
きらめきまとって
Wearing the sparkle
イェーイ！
Yay!
ミュージック・エデュテイメント！
Music Edutainment!
近寄れば溢れる Love Me
If you come close, Love Me overflows
勘違いしてる世界
This misunderstood world
夏は怖いわ今日
Summer is scary today
この部屋ストップ わたゆきあのらびぃです
Stop in this room, I'm Watayuki Ano Lamy
画面のみんなも目の前のみんなも盛り上がる準備できてますか！？
Everyone on screen and everyone in front of me, are you ready to get hyped!?
イェーイ！
Yay!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
いくよ！
Here we go!
雪の国からやってきました
I came from the land of snow
勘違いされても凄く雪女じゃないんです
Even if I'm misunderstood, I'm really not a snow woman
冬は苦手なんです
I'm actually bad with winter
さてさてここいらでとりあえず一杯
Well then, let's have a drink for now
少々お待ち
Wait a moment
かっぽらぱい酔い始め皆さんご一緒に
Starting to get drunk, everyone join in
酔いよいよい！それてさあ飲み交わそう
Drink, drink, drink! Now let's drink together
らびぃの世界へおいでませ
Welcome to Lamy's world
ここは天国かユートピア
Is this heaven or utopia?
あっちもこっちも
Over here, over there
わわわわわわわー！
Wa wa wa wa wa wa wa!
大きい夢叶えましょう 万歳！
Let's make big dreams come true, Banzai!
空の丸からのパン！
Round and round from the sky, bang!
ここはとっておきのシャングリラ
This is a special Shangri-La
掴み取ろうお手の物
Let's grab it, it's easy
世界中幸せお届けします
I'll deliver happiness to the whole world
はい、乾杯！
Yes, cheers!
こんな声だってどうだい？
How about this voice?
（いいいね！）
(Nice!)
耳の奥響くのは？
What's resonating in your ears?
（いいいね！）
(Nice!)
そろそろやめていいかい？
Is it okay if I stop soon?
ここでもう一度のやめなさい
Please stop here once more
（黒歴史なら）
(If it's dark history)
（忘れちゃって）
(Forget it)
もうらびぃのライブはゼロなんだよ
Lamy's lives are at zero now
これ以上やめな、やめろ、やめなさい！
No more, stop, stop, PLEASE stop!
おっとよいよい様は出来た抜き足差し足忍び足
Well then, ready for the tipsy tip-toeing
I’m I’m I’m my lamy-ne lamy-ne
My lamy-ne lamy-ne lamy-ne lamy-ra
Allez! なんか舌が回んないよー！
Allez! My tongue's getting tied up!
最低 乱れて 季節が変わって
The worst, messed up, the seasons change
ここは天国か ユートピア
Is this heaven? Or a utopia?
あっちも こっちも アババババ！ でっかい未来
Here and there, ababababa! A huge future,
語りましょう！ 何で？
let's talk about it! Why?
おまかせ よきよき ここは観覧欄
Leave it to me, good, good, this is the gallery
アルトサフィア
Artosafia
欠片と解けて 叶わない世界
Melting with the fragments, a world that won't come true
ぎゅっと ラミィに染め上げよう
Let's dye it all in Lamy's colors
ほらほら！
Here we go!
まだまだ！
Not yet!
ここから！
From here!
いくよ！
Let's go!
ギター カモン！
Guitar, come on!
推してくれたから
Because you supported me,
頑張ってこれました
I was able to keep going.
本当にありがとうね
Thank you so much.
今度はラミィが背中押してあげるから
This time, Lamy will support you too,
ずっとずっと そばにいてね
so stay by my side forever and ever.
泣きたい時こそ Lamy Loves You!
Especially when you want to cry, Lamy Loves You!
ラミィの世界は終わらない
Lamy's world never ends.
ここは天国だ ユートピア
This is heaven, a utopia.
遊んで 遊んで Happy Happy 夢中ね
Play, play, Happy Happy, I'm obsessed
ほら 幸せでしょう？ 万歳！
See, you're happy, right? Banzai!
空回りからの回り回る ここは最高のサングリアだ
From spinning in circles to turning around, this is the best Sangria
音楽な 涙だって 虹になれる世界中
Even musical tears can become a rainbow all over the world
明日 元気になれ！
Be energetic tomorrow!
みんな大好きです！
I love you all!
今日も今日とて 元気をお届けします！
Today as always, I'm delivering energy to you!
ワン・ツー・にゃん・ハイ！
One, two, nyan, hai!
にゃんぷー！
Ni-nyan-fu!
三食 お昼寝 完備は当たり前
Three meals and a nap, that's a given
にゃんぷー！
Ni-nyan-fu!
（にゃにゃにゃにゃん！）
(nyan nyan nyan nyan!)
あと たまに 褒め撫で でも甘んずる
And sometimes, I'll even settle for a praise and a pet
（にゃにゃにゃにゃん！）
(nyan nyan nyan nyan!)
そしたら 10の愛をあげます 君にきゅん
Then I'll give you ten loves... I'm smitten with you
してもらえます 君とずっと幸せを育てます
I'll let you do it... I'll nurture happiness with you forever
（きゅきゅきゅきゅん！）
(kyun kyun kyun kyun!)
急遽ばかりが 拝啓 この猫である
Always in a hurry, dear reader, I am this cat
（にゃにゃにゃにゃん！）
(nyan nyan nyan nyan!)
特別に 君に触る事 許可する
I'll give you special permission to touch me
（にゃにゃにゃにゃん！）
(nyan nyan nyan nyan!)
素直になれない 本音の尻尾 追いかけて
I can't be honest, chasing the tail of my true feelings...
優しく 掴んでほしい
I want you to catch it gently.
構ってくれなきゃ 寂しいにゃん (にゃん！)
If you don't pay attention to me, I'll be lonely (nyan!)
他の子見てたら いけないにゃん (にゃん！)
You can't look at other girls (nyan!)
人のルールとか 知らないにゃん (にゃん！)
I don't care about human rules (nyan!)
僕が一番 可愛いじゃん
I'm the cutest, aren't I?
にゃん にゃん 君とずっといたいので
Nyan nyan, I want to be with you forever,
僕に首輪を しといてね
so put a collar on me.
わかってないね そんなのなったって
You don't get it, even if it's like that,
僕は君の運命の にゃんにゃん
I'm your destiny, nyan nyan.
夢が醒めてしまうまで
Until the dream wakes up,
鈴の鳴るたび 構ってね
pay attention to me every time the bell rings.
君の愛の全部ください
Give me all of your love.
そしたら ずっとずっと にゃんにゃん だぞ
Then we'll be together forever, nyan nyan.
にゃんと構って！ (にゃんにゃん！)
Nyan-tastic attention! (nyan nyan!)
みんな！ 今日は来てくれてありがとう！
Everyone! Thank you for coming today!
にゃんぷー！
Ni-nyan-fu!
AZKiと一緒ににゃんにゃん声出していこう！
Let's shout out 'nyan nyan' together with AZKi!
いくよ！
Here we go!
アルファ ベータ 構わせた どれだ
Alpha, beta, made you pay attention, which one?
当然 到達 目指すは おめで…
Naturally, reaching for... congrats...
君と行きたいから 果てまでラブ
I want to go with you, love to the end,
だって オメガは 猫マーク
because omega is a cat mark.
臆病で 迷いがちな 小さなハートを
My small heart, timid and prone to getting lost...
受け止めて
catch it,
両手で 包んでほしい
I want you to wrap it in both hands.
これでも 愛情表現にゃん
Even this is an expression of love, nyan.
てか それ そろそろ 気づいてにゃん
So notice it already, nyan.
人の言葉とか 知らないにゃん
I don't know human words, nyan.
僕が一番 大好きにゃん
I love you the most, nyan!
にゃんにゃん 君とずっといたいので
Nyan nyan, I want to be with you forever,
僕に首輪を しといてね
so put a collar on me.
わかってないね そんなのなったって
You don't get it, even if it's like that,
僕は君の運命の にゃんにゃん
I'm your destiny, nyan nyan.
君に愛を尽くすから
I'll give you all my love,
他に移り気は しないでね
so don't look at anyone else.
わかってしまった ズレた瞬間に
I understood it the moment it slipped,
君は僕の運命の にゃんにゃん
you are my destiny, nyan nyan.
夢が醒めてしまうまで
Until the dream wakes up,
猫の手を借りまくってね
keep borrowing a helping hand (cat's hand).
君の愛の全部ください
Give me all of your love.
そしたら ずっとずっと にゃんにゃん だぞ
Then we'll be together forever, nyan nyan.
いくよ！
Here we go!
にゃんと構って！ (にゃんにゃん！)
Nyan-tastic attention! (nyan nyan!)
もっと構って！ (にゃんにゃん！)
More attention! (nyan nyan!)
ありがとう！
Thank you!
This Copia Sounds Out of the Terra
Hey! 振り出せ バンバン 壊せ
Hey! Swing it out, bang-bang, break it!
クラシックな暮らしに メタモルフォーゼ
Metamorphose your classic lifestyle
昔々 そのまた昔
Once upon a time, even further back
絶えてる骸骨に 手を取り憐れだ
Taking the hand of a faded skeleton, how pitiful
狂え！ Ziggity Zagga ギルギル 社会安
Go crazy! Ziggity Zagga, Giru-Giru, social ease
それが普通って 映る 朝のニュース
The morning news shows that as normal
ハイ 待ってメーカー サムライ チャセ ロッティン 重複 理不尽 バカ
Hey, wait maker, samurai, chase, rotten, duplicate, irrational, fool
途上 重低 現状 異文の生 夢見てるバカ
Developing, bass, current state, anomalous life, fool who dreams
Omnisof! The! Terra!
花の Dancing Dancing Rolling Rolling Rolling は My Life
Flowery Dancing Dancing Rolling Rolling is my life
やがて 人生だって 終わってしまうぜ
Before long, even life will come to an end
生殺しだけじゃ 足りないだろ
Being half-dead isn't enough, is it?
Dancing Dancing Rolling Rolling 永遠だって
Dancing Dancing Rolling Rolling, even eternity
派手散らかせ 現状 呼び戻せ 今も 奔放
Scatter flamboyantly, the present, call it back, even now wild
踊りたい 踊りたい
I want to dance, I want to dance
遊び疲れるまで
Until I'm tired of playing
生きてみようぜ！
Let's live it up!
Hey! 引き連れ 身体 パンパン 眠いか？
Hey! Dragging along, body full, are you sleepy?
阿鼻叫喚 響かせ 終わらせ 狂え 猛勢
Make the agonized cries ring out, end it, go crazy, fierce force
おかしい おかしい いつの間に ゾンビ
Strange, strange, when did I become a zombie?
自分の Fucking 音に 敏捷なバカ
A fool who's quick to respond to their own fucking sound
夢はレコードさ 繰り返すだけの 明日か
The dream is a record, is it just a repeating tomorrow?
限りある 理有 もぐもぐなら
If it's limited reasons and munching
一回 足止め 腐って行け 唐突 クレイジー
Stop once, rot away, sudden crazy
君の人生は Fast food 大名声 Oh!
Your life is fast food, great fame, Oh!
滅びの ゾンビ！
Destruction zombie!
ゾンビ 叫べー！
Zombies, scream!
One, two, three, four!
I say Holo, you say Live!
Holo! (Live!)
ビリビリ増す シリアスを歌え！
Sing with a tingling seriousness!
ビリビリ忘れじ 力を歌え！
Sing with a tingling, unforgettable power!
Hey! 乗り越え どんどん 壊せ
Hey! Overcome it, keep on breaking it
クラシックな暮らしに メタモルフォーゼ
Metamorphose your classic lifestyle
吹き抜け生き残る 吹き抜け生きるわ
Surviving through the draft, I will live through it
Omnisof! The! Terra!
花の Dancing Dancing Rolling Rolling Rolling は My Life
Flowery Dancing Dancing Rolling Rolling is my life
やがて 人生だって 終わってしまうぜ
Before long, even life will come to an end
生殺しだけじゃ 足りないだろ
Being half-dead isn't enough, is it?
Dancing Dancing Rolling Rolling 現世見たって
Dancing Dancing Rolling Rolling, even looking at this world
新しきこと やりたいことをやろう
Let's do new things, the things we want to do
踊りたい 踊りたい
I want to dance, I want to dance
遊び疲れるまで
Until I'm tired of playing
生きてみようぜ！
Let's live it up!
One, two, three, four!
This Copia Sounds Out of the Terra
白上フブキ
Shirakami Fubuki
さくらみこ
Sakura Miko
すき すき すきよ すき すき すきよ
Love you, love you, love you, love you, love you, love you
すき すき すきよ I love you!
Love you, love you, love you, I love you!
もぎゅっと もぎゅっと 手を握り
Tight, tight, holding hands
もぎゅっと もぎゅっと 抱きしめ
Tight, tight, hugging you
もぎゅっと もぎゅっと ほっぺしたい I love you!
Tight, tight, want to touch your cheek, I love you!
にゃっはろー！
Nyaho-lo!
こんこんきーつね！
Kon-kon-kitsune!
せーの！ フブミコです！
One, two! We're Fubumiko!
ラストステージ！
Last stage!
みんな盛り上がって行くぞ！
Everyone, let's get fired up!
ドッキドッキな Everyday
Heart-pounding everyday
恋してかなきゃ 損だっていって
Saying it's a loss if you don't fall in love
ハッピーエンドよろしく
Happy end, please
愛情を ぎゅーってピタ
A squeeze of affection, and snug
全部 言ったもん勝ち
Saying it all is winning
推しとピークのコンビネーション
The combination of a fave and a peak
無理よ 推ししか見えない
No way, I can only see my fave
I love you
大好き大好き 好きを好き 大好き大好き 好きを好き 大好き大好き 好きを好き
I love you, I love you, love your love. I love you, I love you, love your love. I love you, I love you, love your love.
I love you
もっと ぎゅっと 手を握って ぎゅっと ぎゅっと 抱きしめて
Hold my hand tighter, hug me tighter
ちゅっ て ちゅっ て ほっぺに したい Love you
I want to kiss your cheek, love you
大好き大好き 止まらない 目が合っちゃう チュッ チュッ チュッ
I love you, I love you, it won't stop, our eyes meet, mwah mwah mwah
大好き大好き 溢れちゃう 大好き大好き 好きを好き
I love you, I love you, it's overflowing. I love you, I love you, love your love
大好き大好き 好きを好き I love you
I love you, I love you, love your love. I love you
無限大好き I
Infinite Love I
はい！ はい！ はい！ はい！ はい！ もっともっとー！
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! More, more!
こんにゃく問答なんてない
There's no point in circular arguments
不思議な奥義 裏技もなし
No mysterious secret techniques or cheat codes
なななな斜めからビビるわけない
Not going to be scared from a diagonal angle
最高しかない チリツモです
Only the best, it all adds up
あれも これも 考えたけど
I thought about this and that
恋が常に インスピレーション
Love is always the inspiration
いいよ いいよ お互い様
It's okay, it's okay, it's mutual
いいじゃん いいじゃん お互い様
It's fine, it's fine, it's mutual
I love you
大好き大好き 好きを好き 大好き大好き 好きを好き
I love you, I love you, love your love. I love you, I love you, love your love.
大好き大好き 好きを好き I love you
I love you, I love you, love your love. I love you
ねぇこっちこっち向いてよベイビー こっちこっち向いてよベイビー
Hey, look this way, look this way baby
ぎゅっと ぎゅっと タッチしてよ OK?
Hug me, hug me, touch me, OK?
こんなんじゃ こんなんじゃ 終われない 付き合っちゃって ベンベンベン
This isn't enough, it can't end like this. Let's go out, ben ben ben
こんなんで こんなんで 終われない
Like this, like this, it can't end
大好き大好き 好きを好き I love you
I love you, I love you, love your love. I love you
全国のみんなー！ 配信のみんなー！
Everyone in the country! Everyone on the stream!
ふぶみこのこと 大好きですかー！？
Do you love FubuMiko!?
ありがとー！ まだまだ盛り上がっていくよー！
Thank you! We're still going to heat things up!
大好き大好き 好きを好き 大好き大好き 好きを好き 大好き大好き 好きを好き I love you
I love you, I love you, love your love. I love you, I love you, love your love. I love you, I love you, love your love. I love you
もっと ぎゅっと 手を握って ぎゅっと ぎゅっと 抱きしめて
Hold my hand tighter, hug me tighter
ちゅっ て ちゅっ て ほっぺに したい Love you
I want to kiss your cheek, love you
大好き大好き 好きを好き 大好き大好き 好きを好き 大好き大好き 好きを好き I love you
I love you, I love you, love your love. I love you, I love you, love your love. I love you, I love you, love your love. I love you
ねぇこっちこっち向いてよベイビー こっちこっち向いてよベイビー
Hey, look this way, look this way baby
ぎゅっと ぎゅっと タッチしてよ OK?
Hug me, hug me, touch me, OK?
大好き大好き 止まらない 目が合っちゃう チュッ チュッ チュッ
I love you, I love you, it won't stop, our eyes meet, mwah mwah mwah
大好き大好き 溢れちゃう 大好き大好き 好きを好き
I love you, I love you, it's overflowing. I love you, I love you, love your love
大好き大好き 好きを好き I love you
I love you, I love you, love your love. I love you
無限大好き I
Infinite Love I
最後だぜ！ みんな大好きだぞー！
It's the last part! I love everyone!
ありがとー！
Thank you!
（息切れ）
(Out of breath)
白上フブキです！
I'm Shirakami Fubuki!
さくらみこです！
I'm Sakura Miko!
せーの、ふぶみこさーん、ですわー！
Ready, we are FubuMiko-san!
みんなー、『無限大好き』可愛かったですかー！？
Everyone, was "Mugen Daisuki" cute!?
えー？ まだ声が小さいぞ？
Eh? Your voices are still small?
そうだよ、もっといきますよ！
That's right, let's go louder!
『無限大好き』可愛かったですかー！？
Was "Mugen Daisuki" cute!?
大好きになっちゃいましたかー！？
Did you end up falling in love with it!?
もっともっと、フンフンになっちゃいましたかー！？
Did you get even more excited!?
すごい... やばい、息あがっちゃう...
Amazing... Oh no, I'm out of breath...
いやー、楽しかったね。
Man, that was fun.
ついにふぶみこもこんな大きなステージで立てたね。
FubuMiko finally stood on such a big stage.
ありがとー！
Thank you!
ポクルムじゃないここは... ポクルムじゃないよね、違うよね？
This isn't Pokurumu... It's not Pokurumu, right? No, it's different?
幕張だよ、みんな！
It's Makuhari, everyone!
ね、せっかくMCやらせてもらえるということで。
Hey, since we get to do an MC section.
恒例の、ちょっとね、コール&レスポンス、やっていこうと思います。みんなやってくれますかー！？
I'd like to do the usual call and response. Will everyone join in!?
やってくれるかー！？
Will you do it!?
よし。ちょっとなんか、みこさんがね、やりたいのがあるって、言ってたんです。何やりたいんですか？
Alright. Actually, Miko-san said she has something she wants to do. What is it?
あのみこさんの『ホロハニ』で、『エリートですかー？』って聞いたら、ちょっと間があったの。
In my 'HoloHoney' song, when I asked "Are you elite?", there was a bit of a pause.
そうだね、ちょっと間があったね。
Yeah, there was a bit of a pause.
ちょっと間があったので、でももう一個ね、新しく聞きたいことがあるんです。
There was a pause, so I have one more thing I want to ask.
聞きたいこと？ 何、何？
Something you want to ask? What is it?
みこ、俺、恥ずかしいか？
Miko, am I embarrassing?
それとも、誇らしいか？
Or, are you proud of me?
みこーれ！
Miko-re!
これってトロッコ問題ってこと？
So is this a trolley problem?
違う、違う、違う。
No, no, no.
ま、せっかくね、ステージ立ってるしね。じゃあ、そうだね。
Well, since we're on stage. Let's see.
「みこーれ」ってみこさんが聞いたら、
When Miko-san asks "Miko-re,"
会場のみんなが「誇らしい」「恥ずかしい」どっちか叫んでください。
everyone please shout either "Proud" or "Embarrassed."
白上が判断します！
Shirakami will judge!
え、本当にそんな、聞き取れるの？その大きい耳だから？
Eh, really? Can you hear it? Because of those big ears?
そう、任せなさい！みんなの声聞いちゃうぞい！
Yes, leave it to me! I'll hear everyone's voices!
え、じゃあいくよ、みんな大丈夫か？
Okay then, here I go. Is everyone ready?
いっぱい叫んでよ！
Shout out loud!
それでは行きます！
Here we go!
みこーれ！
Miko-re!
どっち？どっち？どっち？
Which one? Which one?
「恥ずかしい」だね！
It's "Embarrassed!"
うそー！
No way!
ちょっと！みこぴーの皆さん！
Wait! You Mikopis!
ここは、みこさんがアイドルとして立ってる場所なんですよ！
This is where Miko-san is standing as an idol!
もう一回行こう、みこさん。もっと腹から声出して！
Let's go again, Miko-san. Shout from the bottom of your heart!
じゃあ、みこが言う言葉に続けてください。
Then, please repeat after me.
続けるんかい！
You want us to repeat?!
いくよ！リピート・アフター・ミー、オッケー？
Here we go! Repeat after me, okay?
オッケー！
Okay!
みこ！
Miko!
おーれ！
O-re!
誇らしいよ！
I'm proud!
We're proud!
いやー、これはもう満場一致「誇らしい」だよ。
Wow, that was unanimously "Proud."
じゃあ、ちょっと白上もいいですか？
Then, can Shirakami go too?
白上もね、今日来てくれてるすこん部のみんなに、改めて聞きたいことがあります。
Shirakami also has something I want to ask all the Sukon-bu here today.
白上が、白上のことを何万回愛してる？って言ったらみんな答えてください！
When I ask "How many million times do you love Shirakami?", please answer!
すこん部のみんな！
Everyone in Sukon-bu!
白上のことを何万回愛してる？
How many million times do you love Shirakami?
十万回！
100,000 times!
ありがとう、じゃあ、もっと声出せるよな、みんな。
Thank you. I know you can shout louder than that!
白上のことを、何万回愛してますか？
How many million times do you love Shirakami?
十万回愛してるー！
We love you 100,000 times!
気持ちいいー！気持ちよすぎるな！
That felt great! It felt too good!
あとね、あとね、ライブと言ったらウェーブですよ！
And also, when it comes to a live concert, it's the wave!
そう、なんだけど、横からはあったけどさ、前から後ろってなかったじゃん。
Yeah, but we've had side-to-side waves, but never front-to-back!
じゃあ、前の人から「わー」ってやったら、ちょっと椅子に座っちゃおうか。
Then, once the front people do the "Waa," sit down in your chairs.
そうそう、ずっと立ちっぱもなんなので。
Right, because standing the whole time is tiring.
なので、まず、まず立ってて。まず立ってて。
So, first, everyone stand up. Stand up.
フブミコさん！
Fubumiko-san!
フブミコさん大好きぴ！
We love Fubumiko-san!
やったら、前の人から「わー」で座って、後ろにどんどん続けて座る。
When we say that, the front row sits with a "Waa," and it continues back.
できるよな！ちょっと皆さんの団結した姿見せてください！
You can do it! Show us how united you are!
フブミコさん！
Fubumiko-san!
大好きぴー！
We love you!
これがフブミコさんの波動...波動が、波動が後ろまで、すごい！
This is the Fubumiko wave... the energy is reaching the very back!
きれい！
So beautiful!
ということで、実は自己紹介もしてなかったけど、巻きでお願いしますと。
So, we haven't even introduced ourselves, but we're told to wrap it up.
ただいま、韓国、インドネシアでライブビューイング中です。皆さん見てますか？
Right now, we're live viewing in Korea and Indonesia. Are you watching?
そして、ライブの感想を「#hololivefesEXPO24_DAY2」でSNSにアップしてください！
And please post your thoughts on SNS with #hololivefesEXPO24_DAY2!
そして残念なことに、無料パートはここまでです！
And unfortunately, the free viewing portion ends here!
まだ見たい人はどうすればいいんだい、みこさん？
What should people do if they want to see more, Miko-san?
それはみんな、チケットを買うんだ！
That's simple—everyone, buy a ticket!
買ってー！
Please buy one!
皆さんに もっと火をつけるように
To fire everyone up even more,
エンジンかけていきましょうよ！
let's get our engines running!
一回立ちましょう、皆さん！
Everyone, please stand up for a moment!
立って！立ってー！
Stand up! Stand up!
立って立ってみんな立って立って
Stand up, stand up, everyone stand up!
じゃあ、みこちさんが「好き」って言ったら、
「好き」って返してもらおう。
Alright, if Mikochi says "I love you,"
everyone say "I love you" back!
え、いいじゃん！いいじゃん！
Oh, that's great! That's great!
じゃあ行きますよ、せーの！
Alright, here we go! Ready, set...
好きー！
I love you!
もう一回、好きー！
One more time! I love you!
好きー！
I love you!
ちょっともっと出せるだろ！好きー！
You can do better than that! I love you!
最後！
Last one!
大好きー！
I love you so much!
イェーイ！
Yay!
じゃあいくよ、はいせーの！
Alright, let's do it! Ready, set...
Capture the Moment!
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free part has ended.
Thank you for watching!
無料パートは終了いたしました！ ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free part has ended. Thank you for watching!